<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group Information on Pittsburgh Bridge</title>
    <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group Information on Pittsburgh Bridge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/welcome/</guid>
      <description>So you enjoyed 50 Shades of Grey, The Claiming of Sleeping Beauty, and The Secretary a little more than you let on? You thought to yourself, I bet there’s more of this stuff out there. You browsed a bit and found kink, BDSM, and fetish websites by the dozen. You watched movies. You read stories. Maybe you even checked out a personal ad or two. Then you found us.
Pittsburgh Bridge is the gateway into the world you’ve been imagining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/about/</guid>
      <description>Pittsburgh Bridge is a BDSM peer group primarily designed to provide social interaction and education to people interested in a variety of alternative lifestyles. Pittsburgh Bridge welcomes everyone 18 years of age or older regardless of experience level, providing you are accepting and respectful of all of our members.
Our mission is to create and foster a supportive and enriching environment comprised of mutual respect, acceptance, fluid communication, honesty, and exploration without judgment as we pursue our passions, needs, desires, and enjoyment with regards to BDSM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Generation</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/tng/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/tng/</guid>
      <description>TNG is a group under the Bridge umbrella focused on the needs of the 18-35 age demographic (and their partners) of our community. We welcome all sexualities and gender identification, and any D/s or M/s or any variant power exchange dynamic. As a group we will strive to maintain a safe, respectful, supportive and educational environment for the youngest members of our Pittsburgh Kink community, to further the education and safety of our community as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines for Conduct</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>By attending Bridge events or making use of Bridge resources, individuals agree to adhere to the following guidelines:
Treat other attendees with respect and courtesy. Anyone engaging in rude or disruptive behavior will be warned. If the behavior continues, the person may be asked to leave and not attend further Pittsburgh Bridge events.
Most Bridge events are held in public restaurants. These venues welcome the kink community, but there are acceptable levels of dress and behavior that we must maintain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/resources/</guid>
      <description>National Coalition for Sexual Freedom
NCSF offers legal services for a variety of problems associated with alternative lifestyles. https://www.ncsfreedom.org
Kink Aware Professionals Guide https://ncsfreedom.org/resources/kink-aware-professionals-directory/kap-directory-homepage.html
Munch and Adult Local Link Directory http://findamunch.com
Experienced Kinksters on BDSM Getting into the BDSM Community
https://fetlife.com/groups/3115/group_posts/980383
View PDF: Getting into the BDSM Community Safety in the Scene
https://fetlife.com/groups/3115/group_posts/3252012
View PDF: Safety in the Scene FAQ
https://fetlife.com/groups/3115/group_posts/534028
View PDF: FAQ How to Find a Partner
https://fetlife.com/users/118352/posts/1373232</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>