<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bridge Events on Pittsburgh Bridge</title>
    <link>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bridge Events on Pittsburgh Bridge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Munches</title>
      <link>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/munches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/munches/</guid>
      <description>Munches are social gatherings, which are generally held at restaurants. These are weeknight events which center around food, drink, and discussion with fellow kinksters. They offer a relaxed atmosphere and are an excellent way to meet people and begin to explore kink.
Pittsburgh Bridge Munch: Roland’s7 p.m. on the first Tuesday of the month at Roland’s Seafood Grill in the Strip District.
Roland’s is one of our favorite venues. It offers a large, private area upstairs with a deck, pool tables, a huge bar, a lounge, and all the space we need to stretch out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>If you’re not quite ready for a play event, but looking for something a little wilder than a munch, Happy Hours are the events for you. They’re held at a selection of bars across the city and generally include drinks, dancing, and a party atmosphere. Pittsburgh Bridge Happy Hour is held at 7 p.m. on the second or third Friday of the month at various bars around the city.
Pittsburgh Bridge frequents the following locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/education/</guid>
      <description>Bridge offers three kinds of educational classes that focus on a variety of topics across the spectrum of kink.
Bridge AcademyGenerally on a Saturday from 2-4, some topics run longer. These classes are in depth looks on a variety of different topics. Classes can be structured as demonstrations, lectures, discussions, or hands-on workshops. They cover content on kink dynamics and technical skills of play.
The Next Generation Meeting7 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sloshes</title>
      <link>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/sloshes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pghbridge.github.io/web/group-info/bridge-events/sloshes/</guid>
      <description>Sloshes are booze-centric shindigs. Drink, eat, and be merry in a low key social environment. It’s a bit wilder than a munch, but not quite as intense as a happy hour. You could consider it a cross between the two. Sloshes are designed for those in the 18-35 age demographic (and their partners) to have a relaxed atmosphere to connect with others and begin to explore kink.
TNG sloshes are usually held on the last Friday of the month and rotate between various bars and restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>