<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pittsburgh Bridge</title>
    <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pittsburgh Bridge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pittsburghbdsm.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Munches</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/munches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/munches/</guid>
      <description>Munches are social gatherings, which are generally held at restaurants. These are weeknight events which center around food, drink, and discussion with fellow kinksters. They offer a relaxed atmosphere and are an excellent way to meet people and begin to explore kink.
Pittsburgh Bridge Munch: Roland’s7 p.m. on the first Tuesday of the month at Roland’s Seafood Grill in the Strip District.
Roland’s is one of our favorite venues. It offers a large, private area upstairs with a deck, pool tables, a huge bar, a lounge, and all the space we need to stretch out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>If you’re not quite ready for a play event, but looking for something a little wilder than a munch, Happy Hours are the events for you. They’re held at a selection of bars across the city and generally include drinks, dancing, and a party atmosphere. Pittsburgh Bridge Happy Hour is held at 7 p.m. on the second or third Friday of the month at various bars around the city.
Pittsburgh Bridge is currently reevaluating our Happy Hour locations as we recover from the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/bridge-events/education/</guid>
      <description>Bridge offers three kinds of educational classes that focus on a variety of topics across the spectrum of kink.
Bridge AcademyGenerally on a Saturday from 2-4, some topics run longer. These classes are in depth looks on a variety of different topics. Classes can be structured as demonstrations, lectures, discussions, or hands-on workshops. They cover content on kink dynamics and technical skills of play.
More information on our events coming soon as we get in full swing from the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sloshes</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/tng/sloshes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/tng/sloshes/</guid>
      <description>Sloshes are booze-centric shindigs. Drink, eat, and be merry in a low key social environment. It’s a bit wilder than a munch, but not quite as intense as a happy hour. You could consider it a cross between the two. Sloshes are designed for those in the 18-35 age demographic (and their partners) to have a relaxed atmosphere to connect with others and begin to explore kink.
TNG sloshes are usually held on the last Friday of the month and rotate between various bars and restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website Launch / End of Pandemic Hiatus</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/website2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/website2/</guid>
      <description>A New LookWe are excited to launch our redesigned website - complete with the new logo, color scheme, and running on a new platform under the hood! This new look symbolizes our rebirth after several long years in hibernation running primarily virtual events.
As Twitter seems to be a less and less reliable platform, you can look to this website for more regular updates and event information!
Bridge Reemerges from the Pandemic HiatusWith our Roland&amp;rsquo;s Munch now consistently in full swing, we are looking to get more events back to a regular cadence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/about/</guid>
      <description>Pittsburgh Bridge is a BDSM peer group primarily designed to provide social interaction and education to people interested in a variety of alternative lifestyles. Pittsburgh Bridge welcomes everyone 18 years of age or older regardless of experience level, providing you are accepting and respectful of all of our members.
Our mission is to create and foster a supportive and enriching environment comprised of mutual respect, acceptance, fluid communication, honesty, and exploration without judgment as we pursue our passions, needs, desires, and enjoyment with regards to BDSM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Calendar</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/calendar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines for Conduct</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>By attending Bridge events or making use of Bridge resources, individuals agree to adhere to the following guidelines:
Treat other attendees with respect and courtesy. Anyone engaging in rude or disruptive behavior will be warned. If the behavior continues, the person may be asked to leave and not attend further Pittsburgh Bridge events.
Most Bridge events are held in public restaurants. These venues welcome the kink community, but there are acceptable levels of dress and behavior that we must maintain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/group-info/resources/</guid>
      <description>National Coalition for Sexual FreedomThe NCSF is committed to creating a political, legal and social environment in the US that advances equal rights for consenting adults who engage in alternative sexual and relationship expressions. The NCSF aims to advance the rights of, and advocate for consenting adults in the BDSM-Leather-Fetish, Swing, and Polyamory Communities. We pursue our vision through direct services, education, advocacy, and outreach, in conjunction with our partners, to directly benefit these communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Feed</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/twitter/</guid>
      <description>Tweets by PghBridge </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice For Your First Event</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/advice/</guid>
      <description>Type of EventThe first thing to consider is the kind of social experience that will be comfortable for you, and help you feel encouraged about continuing to explore. Our various events provide different social experiences and atmospheres. It is helpful to select the type of event that best suits your personality.
Do you want a large group setting in which you can see a good range of members of the local scene?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The BDSM Community - It&#39;s Not That Scary After All</title>
      <link>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/not-scary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pittsburghbdsm.com/blog/not-scary/</guid>
      <description>One very common theme that I hear across many new attendees to our munches is an expression of anxiety or uncertainty about joining the community. I am commonly asked if it is appropriate for a new or curious person to just show up, or if it is acceptable to just walk up to others at the event and introduce yourself. The answer to both of those question is emphatically yes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
